Hm.
Good morning. I'm...
I'd like to put on a costume. This brown character is my favorite character.
I'd like to put on the member's stone...
He wants to put on a momo.
Borongo's miniature cat has a face here.
Like a face right here, like in the design.
I'm thinking something cute. Pop-cute.
I think it could be a little less fluffy for some of the members.
Shea, too.
Good morning.
Oh, she has a head, too.
Oh, this guy...
He's so cute!
Does he have ears?
His ears, in case you were wondering.
Oh, yeah, he's cute.
Just as I imagined.
Thank you so much!
I like the pop and cute look.
Like a theme park kind of thing.
I prefer the cuteness of the theme park look.
May's outfit... she wore it here, so...
You didn't take any pictures, did you, Aya?
I should have.
It was so much fun!
But it was on film.
Oh, right.
That was around the time I was going down.
Everybody wears my clothes.
Yes, they do.
I'm not the only one who looks good in them.
I fit in with everyone else.
Mei.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, you look so cute!
Fashion back. Fashion Behind
Fashion backwards.
Oh, my gosh.
Cue.
This place is still different from other idols.
here
thin knees
It's because she's wearing this too!
The glitter scattered on the bish is too much!
Too cute!
OK.
Thank you.
It's already the image on the poster.
Okay.
Let's do it!
And here's a lot of bowlongs.
Here you go.
Okay, here we go.
Wait a minute
Hey, hey, hey.
ah... ah... ah...
ei
Long
Long hand
I will go
OK
OK. OK.
OK OK
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh.
Shhh.
Cute. Cute.
Cute
Ground
This is awesome!
One more pull, Bolong.
Here we go.
Go!
Boom!
Boo!
I can beam from here.
I can beam from here and there.
I can do that.
Beep.
That's great.
Last one.
The last one.
Just a little bit.
No, I'm so happy.
I'll tell you what I'm thinking of.
I want it to look like this, like this.
I want to put a face on this brongo.
or something fluffy.
I had already told them what I wanted to put on.
I'd take that and expand it.
I wanted to take that and expand it and make it look like this.
And then they used glittery materials
or something like that.
These fluffy panniers...
And these legs.
They made it all for me.
I can't wait for the day I get to wear this outfit.
This fluff is seriously too cute
fluffy fluffy fluffy
So many different materials
It's a combination of so many different materials.
This collar is made of glittery material. These collars and stuff, they're really sparkly.
Like lace.
It reflects and sparkles.
or something like that.
I had this quilted
I had them use a quilted material
I asked them to use this material, and it's amazing.
I'm not sure if it's too much to look at, but
this...
Various fabrics were layered on top of each other
to give it volume.
I had them give it volume.
Like this...
It shakes a lot when you shake it.
And my stomach comes out a little.
So be careful with that.
The thinnest part of the body
the thinnest part comes out, so it's fine.
Ears
When we first talked about it, you said, “I'd like to have ears.
I'd like to put on some ears, but
I told him that it would come off during a live performance.
I told him that it would come off during the show.
But then he put the ears on my hat.
I'm so glad you did it!
I'm so happy!
Everything is for Borongo
It's just for Borongo.
Just for Borongo.
It's like an amusement park with beaver bolongos.
Why this Bolongo?
Oh, I don't know. It's a cast member's costume.
It's like this Borongo.
And it's like, “Welcome to the theme park.
Welcome to the theme park.
We haven't decided on the set list yet.
But I'm hoping we can make it look like that.
I hope we can make it like that.I wish I could make it better.
I hope I can make it work.
I don't think everyone needs to be fluffy.
I think it's okay if not everyone is fluffy.
Maybe some fluffy shorts.
I think it's okay if there's a little difference in skirt length
I think it's okay if there's a difference in skirt length.
I want everyone to wear this
Borongo costume
I think everyone should try it on at least once.
In the mirror.
Is this it?
Is this a bolongo? I'm so happy.
I think it's fluffy.
I think people would be attracted to it.
Fluffy.
And I definitely want people to touch them.
They're super fluffy for everyone!
Laughs.
LOL.
LOL!
But, you know, if May wins, this is what it's going to be.
But if May wins, it means this is what it's going to be.
LOL!
Why is that funny?
Because I'm going to bring you
I will bring you the most fun theme park in the world.
Please vote for me.
Please cast your vote for me!
LOL!
LOL, LOL, LOL, LOL, LOL, LOL, LOL...
LOL! LOL!
LOL!